to plant a seed properly it must be
extremely intentional and extremely
clear in your mind there must be a clear
plan I will take them out and it has to
be regular I will take them out every
Friday uh Starbucks on Scottdale and
whatever the crossroad is and I will
give them 45 minutes of my time and not
less I will give them 45 minutes of my
time and I will try to help them I will
support them in in their financial
problems okay that's all in this system
if you don't do that you cannot
succeed oh no Gesa I had some success
earlier in my
life that was an accident okay really
you didn't have any control of it it
came to you because of something you had
done earlier some kindness you had
rendered earlier and you had some
success and then it went away way cuz
you didn't know where it was coming from
you see what I mean
it it's the story of so many successful
people musicians business people
anything actors you know I can't I have
a person in our group who's an Academy
Award nominee I won't say their name but
they can't get a job they can't get any
acting jobs they and they didn't know
why they didn't uh know why what
happened what
changed you were living off an old debit
card and it ran out and you didn't know
where it came from okay I have a lot of
actors now in my uh I teach a lot of
actors this system what do you think is
the way to get an acting
part yeah when the auditions come you
try to find three other people who might
want to audition against you and you
help them and you support them and you
try to pitch them to the director of the
film okay well who was that I can say
her name summer more she's a lady in La
she tried my system she just got a
multifilm part a leading role she just
did it this way she helped other people
get roles you see what I mean with
technique which I'm teaching you right
four steps right so third third part
take them to Starbucks it must be
regular you don't plant a in a day it I
would say once a week try once a week
okay to fix your finances make a regular
date with someone who's struggling and
give them support and help once a week
regularly okay same time each week what
you want you must offer to others
regularly or it won't work doing it once
is not going to make anything happen
it's like throwing a a watermelon seed
uh on the on concrete okay it's not not
enough it has to become a way of life
that you help others it has to become
part of your way of life your regular
way of life okay it has to become an
instinct that when you want something
you try to get it for someone else it
must become instinctual and right now we
have the opposite Instinct what I want I
must take from others I must deny to
others I must compete with others that's
that's our current instinct you see and
to change an instinct is very very hard
okay so it has to be regular it has to
become instinctual oh my husband yelled
at me I have to stop yelling at the
kids instead of getting angry at the
husband your automatic instinct is to
who am I yelling at why how should I
stop my yelling with someone else you
see what I mean like that it must become
an instinct if enough people change that
instinct this world will change
the whole world will change people will
act differently towards each other those
who don't want to be yelled at will stop
yelling in order to not be yelled
at and it will just be an instinct and
the world will